Guide to the Rice University athletic records, 1912-2010 (UA 155) UA 155
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Administrative, 1929-2002 (Boxes 11-45), 201958
  - Subseries D: Historical, Eligibility, and Participation Reports, 1929-1990, 202283
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1970-1971, 202453 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1971-1972, 202452 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1972-1973, 202451 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1973-1974, 202450 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1974-1975, 202449 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1975-1976, 202448 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1976-1977, 202447 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1977-1978, 202446 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1978-1979, 202445 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1979-1980, 202444 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1980-1981, 202443 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1981-1982, 202442 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1982-1983, 202441 (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1983-1984, 202440 (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1984-1985, 202439 (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1985-1986, 202438 (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf1986-1987, 202437 (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - Eligibililty and historical reports, Golf, 1987-1988, 202436 (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1988-1989, 202435 (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Golf, 1989-1990, 202434 (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1967-1968, 202433 (Box 24, Folder 74)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1968-1969, 202432 (Box 24, Folder 75)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1969-1970, 202431 (Box 24, Folder 76)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1970-1971, 202430 (Box 24, Folder 77)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1971-1972, 202429 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1972-1973, 202428 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1973-1974, 202427 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1974-1975, 202426 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1975-1976, 202425 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Swimming, 1976-1977, 202424 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Soccer, 1974-1975, 202423 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1961-1962, 202422 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1967-1968, 202421 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1968-1969, 202420 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1969-1970, 202419 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1970-1971, 202418 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1971-1972, 202417 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1972-1973, 202416 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1973-1974, 202415 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1974-1975, 202414 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1975-1976, 202413 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1976-1977, 202412 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1977-1978, 202411 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1978-1979, 202410 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1979-1980, 202409 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1980-1981, 202408 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1981-1982, 202407 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, 1982-1983, 202406 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1982-1983, 202405 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1983-1984, 202404 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Men, 1983-1984, 202403 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Men, 1984-1985, 202402 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1984-1985, 202401 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Men, 1985-1986, 202400 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1985-1986, 202399 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Men, 1986-1987, 202398 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1986-1987, 202397 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Men, 1987-1988, 202396 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1987-1988, 202395 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1988-1989, 202394 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Men, 1988-1989, 202393 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Women, 1989-1990, 202392 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Tennis, Men, 1989-1990, 202391 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, 1967-1968, 202390 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, 1968-1969, 202389 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, 1969-1970, 202388 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, 1970-1971, 202387 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, 1971-1972, 202386 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, 1972-1973, 202385 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, 1973-1974, 202384 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1974-1975, 202383 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1975-1976, 202382 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1976-1977, 202381 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1977-1978, 202380 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1978-1979, 202379 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1979-1980, 202378 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1980-1981, 202377 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1981-1982, 202376 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, Women, 1982-1983, 202375 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, Men, 1982-1983, 202374 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track & Field, Cross Country, 1983-1984, 202373 (Box 25, Folder 57-58)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track & Field, Cross Country, 1984-1985, 202372 (Box 25, Folder 59-60)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track & Field, Cross Country, 1985-1986, 202371 (Box 25, Folder 61-62)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, Women, 1986-1987, 202370 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1986-1987, 202369 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, Women, 1987-1988, 202368 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1987-1988, 202367 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, 1988-1989, 202366 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, Women, 1988-1989, 202365 (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, Women, 1989-1990, 202364 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Track, Cross Country, Men, 1989-1990, 202363 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1975-1976, 202362 (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1982-1983, 202361 (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1983-1984, 202360 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1984-1985, 202359 (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1985-1986, 202358 (Box 25, Folder 75)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1986-1987, 202357 (Box 25, Folder 76)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1987-1988, 202356 (Box 25, Folder 77)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1988-1989, 202355 (Box 25, Folder 78)
    - Eligibility and historical reports, Volleyball, 1989-1990, 202354 (Box 25, Folder 79)
    - Men's participation, 1982-1983, 202353 (Box 25, Folder 80)
    - Women's athletics, 1975-1976, 202352 (Box 25, Folder 81)
    - Women's athletics, 1977-1978, 202351 (Box 25, Folder 82)
    - Women's athletics, 1978-1979, 202350 (Box 25, Folder 83)
    - Women's athletics, 1979-1980, 202349 (Box 25, Folder 84)
    - Women's athletics, 1981-1982, 202348 (Box 25, Folder 85)
    - Participation reports, 1929-1930, 202347 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Participation reports, 1930-1931, 202346 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Participation reports, 1931-1932, 202345 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Participation reports, 1932-1933, 202344 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Participation reports, 1933-1934, 202343 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Participation reports, 1934-1935, 202342 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Participation reports, 1935-1936, 202341 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Participation reports, 1936-1937, 202340 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Participation reports, 1937-1938, 202339 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Participation reports, 1938-1939, 202338 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Participation reports, 1939-1940, 202337 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Participation reports, 1940-1941, 202336 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Participation reports, 1941-1942, 202335 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Participation reports, 1942-1943, 202334 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Participation reports, 1943-1944, 202333 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Participation reports, 1944-1945, 202332 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Participation reports, 1945-1946, 202331 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Participation reports, 1946-1947, 202330 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Participation reports, 1947-1948, 202329 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Participation reports, 1948-1949, 202328 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Participation reports, 1949-1950, 202327 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Participation reports, 1950-1951, 202326 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Participation reports, 1951-1952, 202325 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Participation reports, 1952-1953, 202324 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Participation reports, 1953-1954, 202323 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Participation reports, 1954-1955, 202322 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Participation reports, 1955-1956, 202321 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
    - Participation reports, 1956-1957, 202320 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Participation reports, 1957-1958, 202319 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Participation reports, 1958-1959, 202318 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Participation reports, 1959-1960, 202317 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Participation reports, 1960-1961, 202316 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Participation reports, 1961-1962, 202315 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Participation reports, 1962-1963, 202314 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Participation reports, 1963-1964, 202313 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Participation reports, 1964-1965, 202312 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Press brochures, 1964-1965, 202311 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Press brochures, 1965-1966, 202310 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Participation reports, 1965-1966, 202309 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Participation reports, 1966-1967, 202308 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Participation reports, 1966-1967, 202307 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Participation reports, 1967-1968, 202306 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Participation reports, 1968-1969, 202305 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Participation reports, 1969-1970, 202304 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Participation reports, 1970-1971, 202303 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Participation reports, 1971-1972, 202302 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Participation reports, 1973-1974, 202301 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Participation reports, 1974-1975, 202300 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Women's athletics, Eligibilitiy and participation, 1974-1975, 202299 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Participation reports, 1975-1976, 202298 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Participation reports, 1976-1977, 202297 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Women's athletics, participation, 1976-1977, 202296 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Participation reports, 1977-1978, 202295 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Participation reports, 1978-1979, 202294 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Participation reports, 1979-1980, 202293 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Participation reports, 1980-1981, 202292 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Participation reports, 1981-1982, 202291 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Participation reports, 1982-1983, 202290 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Participation reports, 1983-1984, 202289 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Participation reports, 1984-1985, 202288 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Participation reports, 1985-1986, 202287 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Participation reports, 1986-1987, 202286 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Participation reports, 1987-1988, 202285 (Box 28, Folder 23-24)
    - Participation reports, 1988-1989, 202284 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Subseries E: Committees, conferences, associations, and events, 1959-2002, 202173
    - Administrative Relations Committee, 1998-1999, 202282 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Clearinghouse presentation, 202281 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Committtee on Athletics Association of Rice Alumni, 1970, 202280 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1971-1975, 202279 (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
    - Committee on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1975-1978, 202278 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Outdoor Sports, 1959-1966, 202277 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Outdoor Sports (Athletic Council), 1968-1971, 202276 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Community Involvement Committee, 1996, 202275 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Community Relations Sub-Committee, 1997-1998, 202274 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Community Relations, 1999-2000, 202273 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Division 1A Athletic Director's meeting, 202272 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Faculty luncheons, 202271 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - N4A, 202270 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - N4A Convention, 1995, 202269 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - N4A Region IV Conference, 1995 Spring, 202268 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - N4A Convention, 1996 June, 202267 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - N4A Region IV, meeting, 1996, 202266 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - N4A Region 5, 202265 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - N4A Convention, 1997, 202264 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - N4A Convention, 1998, 202263 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - N4A Convention, 1999, 202262 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - N4A Convention, 2000, 202261 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - N4A news, 1996-1998, 202260 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - M4A, Student Athlete Recognition Committee, 202259 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - NCAA, Southwest Athletic Conference, 1988-1995, 202258 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - NCAA, Legislative Assistance Interpretations, 202257 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - NCAA/SWC Interpretations, 202256 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - NCAA Convention, 1995, 202255 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - NCAA Complicance Seminar, 1995 May, 202254 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - NCAA Convention, 1996, 202253 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - NCAA Compliance Seminar, 1996, 202252 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - NCAA Convention, 1997, 202251 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - NCAA Foundation Leadership Conference, 202250 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - NCAA Legislation and Interpretation, 2000-2001, 202249 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - NCAA legislation, 202248 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - National Youth Sports Program, 1994, 202247 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Neighborhood Sub-committee, 1995-1996, 202246 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Posse-Flight School Summer Program, 202245 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - R Association, 202244 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - "R" Club, 1956-1957, 202243 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Scholar Athlete Banquet, 1992, 202242 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Southwest Athletic Conference, 1963-1965, 202241 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - SAC information, 1969, 202240 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Southwest Conference, 1991-1993, 202239 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - SAC conference information, 202238 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - SWC Spring meeting, 1991, 202237 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Conference memos, 1969-1972, 202236 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Southwest Conference minutes, 1975, 202235 (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
    - Southwest Conference minutes, 1976-1977, 202234 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Conference minutes, 1977-1979, 202233 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Conference officials, 1968-1972, 202232 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Southwest Conference officials, 1992-1993, 202231 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Spirit Group, 202230 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Sports Carnival, 1996, 202229 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Sports Carnival, 1997, 202228 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Student Association, 202227 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - WAC SAAC, 202226 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Student Athletic Committee, 1993-1994, 202225 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Student Athletic Committee, 1995-1996, 202224 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Student Athletic Committee, 1996-1997, 202223 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Student Athletic Committee, 1997-1998, 202222 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Student Athletic Committee, 1998, 202221 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Student Athletic Committee, 1998-1999, 202220 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Student Athletic Committee (SAC), 1999-2000, 202219 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - SAC, 2000 Fall, 202218 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - SAC, 2001 Spring, 202217 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - SAC Administrative Relations Sub-committee, 1997-1998, 202216 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - SAC Administrative Relations, 1999-2000, 202215 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - SAC Administrative Relations, 2000-2001, 202214 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - SAC Administative, 202213 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - SAC budget, 1998-1999, 202212 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - SAC budget, 202211 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - SAC budget, 2000-2001, 202210 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - SAC budget, 202209 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - SAC Campus Relations Sub-committee, 1997-1998, 202208 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - SAC Campus Relations Sub-committee, 1998-1999, 202207 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - SAC Campus Relations, 1999-2000, 202206 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - SAC Campus Relations, 2000-2001, 202205 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - SAC Campus Relations, 2001-2002, 202204 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - SAC Career Services Sub-committee, 202203 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - SAC Career Services, 1998-1999, 202202 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - SAC Career Services, 1999-2000, 202201 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - SAC Career Services, 2000-2001, 202200 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - SAC Career Services, 2001-2002, 202199 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - SAC Carnival, 202198 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - SAC Community Relations Sub-committee, 1998-1999, 202197 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - SAC Community Service, 2001-2002, 202196 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - SAC handouts, 1998-1999, 202195 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Student Athlete Speaker's Bureau, 202194 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Summer School progress at Rice, 202193 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Summer School, 1999, 202192 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - SSS users, 1999, 202191 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Texaco Advance, 1994-1995, 202190 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Volunteers for Youth, 202189 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Orientation, 1998, 202188 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Orientation, 1989, 202187 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Orientation, 1990, 202186 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Orientation, 1992, 202185 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Orientation, 1997, 202184 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - O-Week Athletic folder, 1997, 202183 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Orientation, 1998, 202182 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - O-Week Athletic folder, 1998, 202181 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Orientation, 1999, 202180 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Orientation, 1999, 202179 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Orientation, 1999, 202178 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - O-Week Athletic folder, 1999-2000, 202177 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Orientation, 2000, 202176 (Box 34, Folder 3-6)
    - Orientation, 2001, 202175 (Box 34, Folder 7-9)
    - Orientation, 2002, 202174 (Box 34, Folder 10-14)
  - Subseries F: Media Guides, 1950-2007, 202119
    - Swimming and diving, 1974-1984, 202172 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Swimming and diving, 1985-1986, 202171 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Swimming and diving, 1986-1987, 202170 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Swimming and diving, 1987-1988, 202169 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Swimming and diving, 1988-2003, 202168 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Men's tennis, 1977-1986, 202167 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Men's tennis, 1987, 202166 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Men's tennis, 1987-2003, 202165 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Women's tennis, 1980-1984, 202164 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Women's tennis, 1985-1986, 202163 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Women's tennis, 1987, 202162 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Women's tennis, 1987-1988, 202161 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Women's tennis, 1987-2005, 202160 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Men's track and field, 1977-1985, 202159 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Men's track and field, 1986, 202158 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Men's track and field, 1987, 202157 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Men's track and field, 1988, 202156 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Men's track and field, 1989, 202155 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Men's track and field, 1990-1996, 202154 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Men's track and field, 1997-2002, 2006, 202153 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Women's track and field, 1981-1985, 202152 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Women's track and field, 1986, 202151 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Women's track and field, 1987, 202150 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Women's track and field, 1988, 202149 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
    - Women's track and field, 1989, 202148 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Women's track and field, 1989-2003, 2006, 202147 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Men's cross-country, 1974, 1978-1979, 202146 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Cross-country, 1980, 202145 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Men's cross-country, 1984, 202144 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Men's cross-country, 1985, 202143 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Men's cross-country, 1986, 202142 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Men's cross-country, 1987, 202141 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Men's cross-country, 1988, 202140 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Women's cross-country, 1981-1984, 202139 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Women's cross-country, 1985, 202138 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Women's cross-country, 1986, 202137 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Women's cross-country, 1987, 202136 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Women's cross-country, 1988, 202135 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Cross-country, 2000, 202134 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - SWC track and field championships, 1986, 202133 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Football, 1950-1963, 202132 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Football, 1964-1974, 202131 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Football, 1975-1978, 202130 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Football, 1980-1981, 202129 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Football, 1982-1984, 202128 (Box 36, Folder 25)